=The Truth (Season 4)=
(Behind-the-Scenes Cast Interview)
You only have one thing to do.
(Talking with the director)
In a bit,
when you're crouching and crying,
(Haomei got it)
look up at him.
Look at this camera.
Let's go.
Okay, crouch down first.
(Crouches obediently)
Try to stay emotional for a few seconds.
(Getting into character)
This is your state right now.
(Filming)
Are you Tui Haomei?
I'm Ke Coffee.
Ke!
It's me.
Is that you?
I...
I'm Tui Haomei!
Haomei?
Why are you here?
Are you alone?
Where's Qian?
Qian?
Where's Qian? Qian!
Qian!
Qian's fine. She's right here.
It's your first time on The Truth,
so what was your first impression
of everyone?
(Li Yi as Tui Haomei)
I was pretty happy.
(Happy)
And I thought they were really nice.
They'd surprise me
during our interactions.
Like Ke Coffee, for example.
It's okay now.
(Softly comforting her)
Okay.
You're not scared at all.
You're amazing.
You can even hold him.
(Scared himself,
but still protecting her)
(Maximum sense of security)
Was there anyone
who was different
from what you expected?
Ding Chengxin, I guess.
I think
my part was probably pretty scary,
and he didn't really
come forward much the whole time.
Come on.
Ke,
come back a little.
(Needs just a little reassurance)
Come sit.
Oh my God!
My legs!
I really scared him.
Sorry about that.
(So sorry)
Yeah.
If you get to come back again,
what kind of role would you want to try?
(Comedy type)
I want to be the funny one.
(The comedians taking photos)
(Running through the scene)
You guys...
Us?
What about us?
Who even are you?
I...
(Introduces himself)
I'm Liu Lian Wangfan.
(Very respectful)
Hello, boss.
(Hypothetically)
If they say that, just jump in.
Did you want to kill him?
Just say, "Shut up".
I'll shut up.
(Message received)
You can jump right in.
If they ask,
"Were you trying to kill him"?
Then when they stop talking,
I'll say that line.
Right.
So you can reveal something right away?
If they want to talk to me first,
I can talk with them?
Right.
(All about improvising)
Just play off them like you did earlier.
It's fine.
(Fully in character)
I'm Liu Lian Wangfan.
This is the key to Manager Tui's office.
You've probably never
been inside, right?
No.
He never lets outsiders in.
Take the key.
Okay.
Go see
shady stuff he's been doing in there.
(Liu Xiaoting as Liu Lian Wangfan)
Away from the crosstalk stage,
you're doing immersive acting
on a variety show.
How does it feel different?
How should I put it?
It's a completely new experience.
(Familiar)
Crosstalk feels familiar.
(Familiar partner)
My partner,
(Familiar audience)
the audience,
(Familiar theater)
and the theater.
(Unfamiliar setting)
Now I'm somewhere unfamiliar,
(Unfamiliar people)
with people I don't know.
I still have to keep everything moving.
So,
there's a lot more going on in my head.
I'm not as relaxed
as I am doing crosstalk.
During filming,
how did it feel
acting opposite Jin Jing?
I thought she was incredibly relaxed.
I'm here to settle a score.
With who?
Jin Cardashian.
You're here for me?
No way.
You haven't been home
for seven days and nights.
I knew you'd be here.
Which home of mine
do you mean?
Compared with me,
I've done very few variety
or reality shows,
so
I'm a little limited in what I can do.
While interacting with the players,
did anything really stick with you?
What stuck with me most was Jin Jing.
She said maybe I
could join Amazing Night 3.
(Special invite from Jin)
Thank you.
If anyone
from Amazing Night 3 sees this,
let's talk.
(Applying online)
I want in too.
(Pretty please)
When you said,
"How am I any worse“
“than He Yiwei"?
what were you thinking?
Who's that He-something-wei?
He Yiwei.
(That's me)
That's him.
That guy.
Tell me, how am I worse than him?
You're worse in every way!
(That's his reputation)
I was just making fun of myself.
That was meant to be self-deprecating.
Is it my looks or my height?
What's the difference?
It's obvious.
(Comparison steals your joy)
I don't think I'm that much worse.
(Hurt)
How do you see Liu Lian Wangfan
as a character?
How is he different from you?
He's not really a bad guy.
Even though he had a motive to kill,
everything he did was for his sister.
She'd been through some terrible things,
and it left her miserable and withdrawn.
From beginning to end,
he was doing it all for his sister.
I think he's a good brother.
I wouldn't call him a bad person.
If it were me,
the main difference
is I wouldn't be that impulsive.
But just like him,
I'd do anything to protect my family.
=The Truth (Season 4)=
(SVIP updates Wed & Thu at noon)
(VIP updates next day at noon,
one week early)